I deliver you from any satanic covenant -
covenant of attitude, covenant of character - be delivered!
Be delivered!
Deliver and release yourself!
Open your lips and begin to release yourself from any satanic covenant -
covenant of attitude, covenant of character, and covenant of behaviour.
Begin to release yourself!
Get yourself out of this covenant!
You are released!
Be released!
As the fire of the Holy Spirit descended on the people following the prayer of release from Prophet T.B. Joshua,
the evil spirit that had destroyed this young woman is exposed and begins to manifest.
She's a prostitute.
Spirit of anger.
The spirit that pushed her to prostitution and criss-crossed her body with tattoos
is now being consumed by the fire of God as she is about to be set free.
You are released!
Be released! In Jesus Christ's name we pray!
TESTIMONY TIME
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Ayisha Idirisu.
I'm from Mali, but we are based in Ghana.
And the woman standing beside you, who is she to you?
She's my mother.
I want to thank the man of God for delivering me last Sunday from the spirit of prostitution.
I'm a professional prostitution.
You mean you're a professional prostitute.
Yes, an international prostitute.
Professional prostitute, what do you mean by that?
I put my pictures on Facebook and Instagram so that I'll be communicating with men.
I will be communicating with them to have an affair with them so that they will pay me.
It all started when I was 9 to 10 years old.
On my way to school, I met an old man.
He tricked me and gave me money to sleep with me in an unfinished building.
That is when I started having that spirit of prostitution - since that age.
I would be running after men, but not ugly men. That spirit didn''t like ugly men.
Only handsome men. If he was handsome and I liked him, no matter who he was,
if I looked at him, I had to have him.
So that is how it started.
So you mean at the age of 10 years, you started meeting men?
Yes.
And how many men did you meet every day?
Sometimes two, three or four.
Does that mean while you were doing all this, your parents - your mother and father -
they were not there to see you?
My father divorced my mom when I was very young.
So I was the one taking care of my mom, my sisters and brothers.
At that age I started being with men, going to clubs with friends,
smoking weed and cigarettes, drinking alcohol.
Sometimes I would be with my friends -
maybe we were three or four - and one man would just tell us, "I want all of you".
We would go to the man's place.
Then the man would tell us that we must be together as lesbians before he would have an affair with us.
We would be together as lesbians before he would have an affair with us.
Then he would pay us and we would go back home.
So how many of you would be together that the man would be sleeping with? How many of you?
Sometimes, we were three or four and sometimes two.
Sometimes two girls, sometimes three girls, sometimes four girls.
That was how I started doing it.
I was a prostitute when I met my baby's daddy.
At what age now?
When I met my baby's daddy, I was 15 years old.
The guy tried to change me but he couldn´t change me.
I got pregnant for him and I give birth in 2012.
My mom told the guy's family that he had to marry me.
So they came and paid my bride price.
One day, I was at my mom's place and somebody called me that the guy brought her and my friend
inside his house so I went straight to their house and fought with the girl.
The guy's mother called me and told me that her son will not marry me again
so I should just go away.
That was how I left and rented my own apartment.
I just told myself that if I didn't get married again, I should go back to my work of prostitution
because that would make me survive and take good care of my family.
So I just went back and rented an apartment.
I called guys, sometimes two guys.
I would be having an affair with two guys, three guys, four guys in the same night.
So that was how I continued to do it.
I was still forcing myself to change but no solution.
Because if I stopped, my family would not eat; my family would not do anything.
I went to a native doctor to tell the native doctor,
"This work I'm doing - I'm a prostitute - I want to stop it but I need quick money.
I need blood money so that I can take care of my family".
The native doctor said, "Ok" and told me to bring 8000 Ghana cedis.
I went and borrowed the money.
The native doctor told me that around 10 o'clock, we would be going somewhere.
I didn't know that place.
At 10 o'clock, I went up to the native doctor's place and he took me to a cemetery.
He told me that I would bathe three times a day.
That was Wednesday, Friday and Sunday.
I said, "Okay, if that will make me get the quick money, no problem. I will do it".
I followed the native doctor in doing it but no solution.
I went to pastors.
Not one pastor, not two pastors. Some of them would take my money,
some of them would be sleeping with me.
But no solution. I accepted that I had to stop this prostitution.
It was not for me. But if I stopped, my family would not eat.
So I needed quick money.
You needed quick money.
Yes.
Ok. So why did you now go to all these pastors? What were you looking for?
Ghanaian pastors will tell you that they will give you lotto numbers, plenty of things.
So you also went to them for help?
Yes, for help.
And what happened after that?
At long last, they would just sleep with me and tell me that I would get the money.
But I would not get it.
I would sleep and dream that I was swimming inside water.
When I then woke up in the morning and saw a handsome guy going
or sitting there, I would just go straight to that guy and look at him, just like that.
How did you look at them?
I would just look at him.
Just like that. I would just look at him.
So that he would fall for me and have an affair with me.
But for him to date me - no way.
He would just promise me, "I will date you; I will marry you".
So this was how you would get men?
Yes, that's how I would get men.
I didn't go for ugly men because that spirit in me didn't like ugly men.
I would only be with handsome men because when I got them and slept with them,
I would just take my money and go my way.
I didn't know what would happen to them.
Okay, you said while you were looking for quick money, you went to do some rituals.
Explain to us again: You said you were taken to a graveyard.
Yes, the native doctor took me to a graveyard and I had to get naked.
There was a certain water opposite, just behind the grave.
He told me to get naked, go inside, swim and take anything I want.
I did it three times.
He gave me an egg to put inside the water and old currency coins.
I threw them inside the water and went back but there was no solution.
I didn't go there again.
I have one friend in Nigeria - a guy.
I met him on social media - Facebook.
I told him that I needed blood money because I had to take care of my family.
He asked me, "You don't have a father?"
I said, "I have a father but he doesn't take care of us
and my mother doesn't work, so I'm the one taking care of my family".
So he said, "Okay, I will introduce you to an occultist".
He introduced me to the occultist.
He told me to bring a certain amount of money.
But I couldn't get the money and that was why I didn't go and join the cult.
After that, I just decided to travel outside the country
so that I would stop that prostitution and get money.
I called one agent and the agent told me that he could help me to travel
- to Saudi Arabia first. I said, "Okay".
I put my apartment up for rent, sold everything I had.
I even borrowed money and gave it to the agent.
That is the visa so that I could travel to Saudi Arabia. That was March last year.
He did everything and told me that I was going to work in a company.
I told him, "Okay". When I arrived in Saudi Arabia, they took me to a certain house.
The boss inside the house told me that I should bring my passport.
I asked, "Why? I did my part. I got this passport with my money".
He told me, "I bought you. You are my slave now".
I said, "I paid a lot of money before I got here".
He said, "No, I bought you. I paid the agent 250 million Ghanaian cedis".
I then called the agent.
So you were sold for 250 million Ghanaian cedis?
Yes
To that man?
To that man.
I then called the agent but the agent didn´t pick the call.
I called my mom to tell her.
She said that I should just manage it.
So I said, "Ok, no problem".
So you were sold to this man to be doing what?
To serve him and his family for good two years as a housemaid.
before they released me to return to my country.
When I was inside the house, they were treating me very bad.
Sometimes, I would eat once in three days.
And that was not a real meal - maybe a banana or an orange and then just go to sleep.
They would be beating me up; they would do very bad things to me.
I couldn't sleep. I would sleep maybe at around 3 am in the morning,
wake up at 4 am in the morning and start working.
The house was a three-storey building and I would clean the house.
Every day, I had to clean the house with my hands.
I then made up my mind that I had to survive in this house. If not, I would just die.
My family didn´t even know where I was.
When I was working, they didn't even pay me money.
And it was because of money that I went to Saudi Arabia.
I said to myself that I had to get this man - the woman´s husband. If I did something...
You mean your boss?
Yes, my boss.
If I did something with him, I would be okay.
I would be a little bit okay in that house.
They would not treat me the way they were treating me before.
One day when the madam and the children went out, my boss said I should bring him a coffee.
After I had done the coffee and brought it into his room, I was face-to-face with the man.
When the man just looked at my eyes, he started having an affair with me.
That was how it started. That was the same way I got the man´s son too.
I was having an affair with the man and with the man´s son inside the house.
But they didn't know.
So you used the power in your eyes?
Yes.
I would just look face-to-face at them.
When I looked face-to-face at them, I would not shine my eyes or do anything.
I would just look at you and you had to have an affair with me.
The way they were treating me before reduced.
If the woman was beating me or not giving me money to eat,
the man and his son would just disgrace the woman and insult her.
But both of them didn't know that I was doing something with each of them.
That was how it was going on inside the house.
I said, "No, I didn't come here for that prostitution.
I came here to work with my hands. So why am I doing this? I must get out of the house".
I called one of my friends. She is in Dubai.
I told her about that. My friend said, "These Arab people - that is how they are.
So if you didn't do something bad to them, you could never survive in their house.
They will even kill you. So maybe you should take something and run away to the police station".
So I took one of his son's phones.
Your friend advised you that if you wanted to leave the house, you must do something wrong.
Yes.
So what did she advise you to do?
I took one of his daughter's phones and when they were sleeping,
I just jumped over the wall - it was not a small wall.
I jumped over the wall and went outside.
The police were everywhere.
When I went outside, I did not have papers. They asked and I said I didn't have them.
The police took me to the police station and asked me why I had run away.
I told them how they were treating me inside the house and they called my boss.
My boss said, "Ayisha has told me. I don't like Ayisha again".
I spent six days in the police station.
My boss came with a certain man...
Can you explain to us - why did you steal something from them?
So that my boss would say, "I don't like this girl again; I don´t want to work with this girl".
So you did that so that they would send you out of the house.
Yes.
When I was in the police station - one day, I saw my boss with a certain man.
They came and they were just talking.
He just said, "This is the girl I bought and I want to sell her to you".
I didn't say anything and my boss said, "This is your boss.
This is the money he has given me so this is your new boss who you will work for".
I said: "Okay, no problem".
So you were sold to another man.
Another man.
I said: "Ok, no problem" because I didn't have a choice.
If I didn't agree, I would just be in the prison, nowhere to go.
They would even kill me because they didn't know my family.
So I said, "Okay, no problem".
I followed the man to his house.
That house was even more horrible than the first house.
They were treating me very bad.
I couldn't sleep. I couldn´t do anything inside the house.
I would work for the woman and the woman would take me to her family and I would work at that house.
I would go to another house to work so that they would pay the woman.
And I would go to another house to work.
They would give the woman money. So I was just working house to house.
So that was what I was doing at the second house.
I said to myself, "These people will kill me.
I will never go back to my country so I must do something
because it is for the sake of my family that I came here.
I came up with the same plan as in the first house.
I said to myself, "I must have this woman's husband. If I have this woman's husband,
I think my problem will be solved a little bit".
One day the woman was sleeping and her husband was inside the parlour.
I just got naked and went straight to the husband and the husband had a...
You went naked?
Yes, I went straight to the husband and he had an affair with me.
In the morning, the husband called his wife and told her
that the way they were treating me inside the house was not good. They should be careful.
Now tell us what happened? How did you manage to return to Ghana?
I ran away and the police saw me.
They told me,"This girl has been brought to the police station every day.
We are tired with this girl. She must go to jail".
That was how they put me into jail.
I spent like three and a half months inside there.
When I was inside the jail, I saw many Africans -
Nigerians, Ugandans, Kenyans and Ghanaians.
As I'm a Muslim, I don't pray.
When I was at my first boss' place, I used to watch Emmanuel TV on YouTube.
When I went to prison, I saw that when the girls were praying,
they would mention the name of the man of God - "God of T.B. Joshua, help us!"
Then I said, "Although I am a Muslim, I must join in these prayers.
Maybe God will set me free and I can go back to my country".
I joined them; we all prayed.
We always prayed - in the morning and at night.
So one day I was just sitting there.
I didn't even know I would be free because it was not yet my time.
I had to spend maybe two years or one and a half years before they would bring me back to Ghana.
But I spent just three and a half months.
They just told me, "Ayisha, your visa is ready to go back to Ghana".
That was how I came back Ghana.
Miss Ayisha Idirisu & Mother
Deliverance Testimony
So you were joining a group of people while they were praying together,
watching Emmanuel TV, asking God to rescue them.
If God can rescue them, they will give their life to Christ.
So you joined this group of people and one day you were called that you needed to go back to your country.
Yes, they released me and people were still inside the prison but they just released me without any reason.
When I went to Ghana, I had made up my mind that I would come to The SCOAN for deliverance
because I knew that I needed deliverance.
I called one of my girlfriends because I didn´t have anywhere to stay.
I called her and my friend said I should come.
When I got to the house, I told my friend, "I need to go to The Synagogue".
My friend asked me, "To do what?" I said, "Deliverance".
And my friend just told me, "Can deliverance give you money?
Why don't you start your prostitution again?"
I said, "Okay, it's true. Even if I get deliverance, who will feed me? Who will feed my family?"
So I should just continue my prostitution.
That was how I continued doing prostitution when I came back to Ghana.
One day, I dreamt. I saw a woman.
She was like a goddess. I saw her in my dream.
When I woke up in the morning on that fateful day, one of my girlfriends showed me something on her phone,
"I saw a tatoo on the internet yesterday night. It was very very nice". I said, "Let me see the tattoo".
When she showed me the tattoo, it was the same tattoo I had dreamt about and I went to have it done.
So you dreamt you saw this image in your dream and the following day you went to have this tattoo?
Yes.
So what was the reason for this? And what do you actually do with this tattoo?
This tattoo I have - whenever I go out, I must expose my body.
So that when people see me, they would just have feelings for me.
So you were having this and each time you went out to look for men, you had to...
Can you tell us - how did you normally dress? We can see some pictures here on the board.
And when you dressed like that, what were you actually looking for?
Okay, this dress was like - maybe when I was going out in the morning to the beachside or hotel.
That was how I dressed so that I would attract men.
This would also be in the morning because in the evening I didn´t even dress like this
- this was even long.
In the evening I didn´t dress like this at all - that was at the beachside.
I had to dress like this so that I would be attracting men.
Maybe four or three men in a day - I would be having an affair with them.
When you came back from the journey you went to, you continued your prostitution.
Yes.
Okay. Can you continue?
Three weeks ago, I was just sitting inside my room by myself.
It was evening time.
My friends - we were four inside the room - were going out to a club. It was a Friday.
They told me, "Let´s go". I said, "No, I don't feel like going out today. You should go".
They said, "You don't have money anymore.
Your mom is even sick and you must send money to your mom".
I said, "I don't feel like going out so you people should go".
Since I came back, I never prayed.
I had even forgotten that I had prayed and that God had set me free from the prison.
Since I had come back, I had forgotten to pray.
I was just sitting there on that fateful day.
I said, "Today I must pray because this work is not for me. I don´t want to do this work again".
So I just prayed, "God of T.B. Joshua, please save me. You are the Father of the poor.
Help me and change me in this situation".
And I slept. I saw the man of God in my dream.
He told me, "Without deliverance, you have nowhere to go".
And you have never met with the Man of God before?.
No, no, no,
You have never been here?
I have never met him before.
So I replied to him, "Can deliverance give me money?" because...
Yes, inside my dream and the man of God just told me straight, "With God all things are possible".
That was when I woke up from my dream.
I then said to myself, "I need to go to The Synagogue, no matter what".
But that day - it was like I hadn't eaten for two days.
I was taking only water; I didn´t even have a penny on me.
I was using an iPhone 6 and if you sell it, it costs quite a bit.
I said to myself, "Ok, let me sell my phone and come down here".
So that was how I sold my phone and came here last week Sunday.
Now tell us: How did you receive your deliverance during the mass prayer when you came last Sunday?
Yes, I was sitting there.
When the mass prayer started, it was like hell. All over my body was fire.
Something just told me to go straight and grab the man of God's leg.
But I was just standing there.
I said, "I must go to him and grab this man´s leg because he was disturbing me with the prayer".
I just took one step, and I didn't see anything again.
MIss Ayisha Idirisu & Mother
Deliverance Testimony
So during the mass prayer, while the prayer was going on,
that evil spirit inside of you was pushing you to go forward to the man of God to grab his leg.
Yes.
When you made an attempt to do that, what did you say happened to you?
I didn't see anything again.
I just saw myself that I was sitting here.
So you mean you got your deliverance last Sunday?
Yes, I got my deliverance. I didn't even feel like smoking or taking alcohol.
So before, you used to smoke and drink. Can you tell us what kind of cigarettes you took in the past.
I smoked weed and cigarettes, and I drank a lot of alcohol.
But since that day...
Since your deliverance.
No, I haven´t even attempted to do that or feel something for men and all that.
Since last Sunday.
Yes, since last Sunday.
You don´t feel for men. What do you mean by you don´t feel for men?
If it was like before, I would just feel something like, "Go out and get men".
But since my deliverance, that thing is not talking to me anymore.
I don´t have bad dreams anymore. I used to fly inside my dream a lot.
Every day I was inside the water swimming but since my deliverance - no more.
Shall we put our hands together wonderfully for our Lord Jesus Christ!
The great Deliverer who has delivered our sister from the spirits of prostitution and marine spirit
that had possessed her for a very long time.
And she has explained to us how she has indeed used this power to destroy men and those around her.
Is your mom aware of this job you were doing?
Because you said that you were actually bringing money home.
No, my mom is not aware because she doesn't have a choice.
She doesn't have money, she doesn't have a helper.
So when I brought her money, she wouldn´t ask me anything.
So each time you come back home with money that you got from prostitution,
she didn´t even bother to ask you?
No.
Does this mean that you have never gone to school? You didn´t go to any college? Or study?
No, no. I just stopped school when I was in JSS 2.
You stopped schooling when you were in JSS 2. Why did you stop?
Because I didn't have money. I didn´t even have that money to go to school.
And my mom didn´t have.
So that's why I said, "I must stop and do that prostitution. It will help me".
And now to the glory of God, today you are delivered.
You are set free completely from this spirit that had been tormenting you for a very long time.
Before we listen to your mom, what word of advice do you have for young ones
who are watching you right now? Because in the first place you left Ghana
because you were looking for quick money.
And when you got to Saudi Arabia, your situation grew worse.
Can you tell us: What advice do you want to give to young ones who are watching you
and listening to you right now?
Ok, my advice is especially to young girls.
They should not rush in life.
No matter who you are, no matter how poor you are, just be patient
and wait for God's time because God's time is the best.
Those women - if their daughters bring them money and they don´t ask where they got the money from,
they should be very careful and ask their daughters where they got the money from.
Because that is how we girls do it and have money to give to our parents.
So those women should be very careful and advise their children.
Shall we put our hands together wonderfully for our Lord Jesus.
We believe that this word of advice you are giving to young ones all over the world
is a typical example that they must be content in life.
That whatever situation you find yourself in, God's time is the best.
When it's God's time for you to achieve something, your tension and pressure will never be required.
We thank God today that God Almighty has indeed brought you out of the darkness
to this marvellous light.
Now you can stand to testify to the goodness of God
that the only solution to this problem is to have Jesus Christ.
Accept Him with all your heart and when you have Him, you have everything.
We thank God for your life.
Let's quickly listen to your mother, who we believe has one or two things to say.
Miss Ayisha Idirisu & Mother
Deliverance Testimony
Origninally I'm from Niger but I live in Ghana.
Okay, Mamma. Can you tell us: what do you know about your daughter?
I believe you've listened to one or two things that she has just said.
Miss Ayisha Idirisu & Mother
Deliverance Testimony
My daughter at the age between 9 and 10, became very stubborn.
Anything I told her, she didn't listen to it.
Miss Ayisha Idirisu & Mother
Deliverance Testimony
When she was between 9 and 10, I divorced the father.
She was supposed to be in JSS 2 but she stopped schooling.
So the mother then asked the daughter, "Why have you stopped schooling?"
The daughter said, "Because you don't have money to sponsor me in my education anymore,
I want to go and live my life somewhere else".
Were you aware that your daughter was doing prostitution?
Miss Ayisha Idirisu & Mother
Deliverance Testimony
In the beginning, I didn't know what job she was doing. It was later that I found out.
Since she received her deliverance, what changes have you seen in her?
Miss Ayisha Idirisu & Mother
Deliverance Testimony
Since her deliverance last Sunday, everything about the daughter has changed.
She doesn't go anywhere; she stays in the house.
She used to chat - she doesn´t chat anymore.
Even when there's no food in the house, she doesn't go out.
She is always inside. She doesn't have any urge to go out.
What advice do you have for parents who are listening to you,
looking at where you are actually coming from?
What advice do you want to give to parents listening to you right now?
Miss Ayisha Idirisu & Mother
Deliverance Testimony
The first one I want to say is that divorcing is very bad.
The second one I have to say is that because of the business the daughter was doing
and bringing money home, she was not able to control her.
So parents, we should be able to control our children,
wherever they bring us something from outside.
We thank God for your life, Madam, and we know that God Almighty has delivered your daughter.
We just want to advise you, our sister, that now God Almighty has set you free
from all these evil spirits that caused you to be prostituting,
we pray that God Almighty in His infinite mercy will grant you the grace
to live the rest of your life for Him.
Make the Word of God the standard for your life.
Be close to Christ Jesus and receive instruction from Him.
We pray that God will grant you the grace to do so, in Jesus' name.
Amen!
Testimony Continues
My name is Ayisha Idirisu. I´m from Ghana.
The lady beside me is my mom.
We are originally from Niger.
I was the lady who was delivered from the spirit of prostitution and now I'm free, in Jesus' name.
I have seen a lot of change - no more bad dreams.
I used to dream that I was flying, swimming in water,
eating in the dream and even having affairs in the dream.
Since I have been delivered, I am okay.
I no longer dream about those types of things.
I used to feel like having relationships with guys.
If I looked into a guy's eyes, he would just fall for me but now, I have tried it and it is no more.
So that spirit of lust has completely gone?
It has completely gone.
I used to smoke a lot; I used to smoke weed and cigarettes.
I don´t smoke, I don´t take alcohol anymore.
I don't even have the urge to do that again.
And during your testimony you said before, you would go on the internet,
use Facebook, post your pictures to attract men.
And now that you're delivered, what can you say about all of that?
I have stopped. I just planned that when I return to Ghana,
I will block all of my Facebook contacts and internet.
I'll block everything so that I will begin a new life.
Before you came to The SCOAN, just tell us the kind of area that you are living in before.
I was living with my friends in a ghetto house.
That was where I lived with my friends and did prostitution.
That place you are coming from is actually from an area where you are constantly with people
that are involved in that prostitution.
As you are going back to Ghana now, do you mean you are going to change that environment?
Yes, sure. I´m going to change that environment.
We thank God once again for our sister's life.
We know that the evidence of Christ Jesus is lives changed.
We just want to hear one word from your mother.
Mrs Hajara Ahmedu
Nigerian Living In Ghana
Her name is Mrs. Hajara Ahmedu and she´s from Ghana but originally from Niger.
I want to thank God for everything because now, my daughter has changed; I am happy.
My mom said she wants to thank God for everything because now, I have changed.
I have really changed and she is very happy. She wants to thank God for that.
We've heard all from our mother. We thank God for the deliverance in the life of our sister.
Sister, we are here right now with a message from Prophet T.B. Joshua.
The Man of God Prophet T.B. Joshua said that he really wants to support you in every area of your life
as you're going back to Ghana now to start a new life.
On behalf of Prophet T.B. Joshua and Emmanuel TV partners worldwide,
we are here to present to you this cash gift of 2000 US Dollars
and also the Word of God, "The Mirror" which is just an encouragement
for you to stay close to Jesus and make His word the standard for your life.
I can't even talk. I'm really shocked.
Seriously, because I didn't even expect this at all.
I never expected that at all. I'm really shocked.
I'm going to use this money to start a new life; to start a new business.
I thank God, Emmanuel TV, the man of God and Emmanuel TV Partners.
Thank You, Jesus, I'm free.
I am free; thank You, Lord!
Wow, thank You, Jesus.
Right now, we believe many people are watching you.
Even girls that are involved in prostitution.
Your people that knew you very well in the past may be watching you right now.
What is your advice to people that are involved in such a lifestyle?
My advice especially for ladies like me: They should change.
No matter who you are, just change and get close to God.
With God all things are possible.
Thank You, Jesus Christ. We thank God for your life, sister.
We pray that God will give you the grace to continue to stay close to Jesus
and make use of this wonderful gift.
We believe that you're going to come back with more wonderful testimonies, in Jesus' name.
Amen. Thank You, Jesus, I am free!
I'm very happy. Thank You, Jesus!
TT: Jacqueline Margaret
RV: Mel Flowers 25/10/2018